<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Products on Matteo Ingoglia</title>
        <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Matteo Ingoglia</description>

         
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Automations</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/automatisations/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description> We offer the automations of Joutech.&#xA;Joutech is a company that since its beginning has been guided by 4 fundamental principles: quality, respect, flexibility, and support. They have been operating in the field of material handling in the wood industry and other industries for over 30 years.&#xA;They deliver automation products: wood cutting and processing, wood loading for all types of machines such as nailing lines or sawmills.&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Crosscutting Machinery</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/crosscutting/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description>Lines for Cutting Long Wood to Size Two Types of Crosscutting&#xA;Continuous Crosscutting Push Crosscutting with 1 Blade Push Crosscutting with one Blade&#xA;Crosscutting Machines to Cut More Board Layers&#xA;Play Video on YouTube And Package Cutters to Cut Entire Packages&#xA;Request a personalized offer</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Machines and Production Lines for Wooden Pallets</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/productionlines/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description> We offer machines and pallet lines from OMEV Erba, a company that has been operating in the sector for over 60 years. Omev produces machines and lines for the production of standard and customized pallets, cases, and reels.&#xA;We have a wide range, from small batch lines to fully automated, high-capacity, and flexible pallet production lines with up to 600 units per hour (EPAL type).&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Sawmill</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/sawmill/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description> We offer sawmill machines from CML Engineering&#xA;The knowledge that goes into the technology puts CML ENGINEERING Srl in a world-leading position in the manufacture of wood cutting machines and systems. Its products are characterised by low operating costs, high productivity, precision, and durability. The production of automatic circular saws is highly flexible and includes more than 30 different models. The wide product range is supported by a production capacity that can meet even the most demanding requirements.&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Used Machines in These Categories</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/used/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description>We also offer used machines which represent an excellent solution with a reduced price.&#xA;Are you interested in learning more about our used machines?&#xA;Contact us and we will find the best solution for you and your company.&#xA;Request a personalized offer</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Wood (boards, beams, pressed blocks)</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/wood/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description>We collaborate with German, Swiss, and Polish sawmills to offer the following material:&#xA;Long Boards – all standard and non-standard sizes Boards cut to size – all standard and non-standard sizes Beams – all standard and non-standard sizes Pressed blocks Request a personalized offer</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Wood Dryers</title>
                    <link>https://www.ingoglia.de/en/products/wood-dryers/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <description>We offer the container wood dryers from the Italian manufacturer Incoplan.&#xA;Incoplan&amp;rsquo;s drying systems for the treatment and evaporation of wood are 100% made in Italy, with high performance and durability, efficient and sustainable.&#xA;We offer a wide range of dryer models: From 8 to 300 cubic meters Hot water supply 90°C, water 119°C, steam, diathermic oil, electricity, heat pump, gas burner. Possibility of installation inside or outside. Automatic process management system. Applications: Pallet (ISPM 15) Firewood Strips Exotic wood Hard woods Conifers/resinous We offer 4 of Incoplan&amp;rsquo;s main and most popular products, which have proven themselves to many customers across Europe over the years:&#xA;</description>
                </item>
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
